http://constructionpartner.com/privacy.php

WHAT DO YOU GET?
Labor Compliance
Construction Accounting Software for Estimating and Management
Privacy Policy
We at Construction Partner thank you for visiting our website. Because we are committed to respecting the privacy of our website visitors, this website Privacy Policy Statement describes the information we may collect from you during your visit to our site, how we may use it, and how we will protect the information which you may opt to provide. This statement explains our efforts to balance our business interests in collecting and using the information we receive from you, with your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information that you share with us.
Personally Identifiable Information
Personally identifiable information includes your name, address, phone number, email address or any other information which might reasonably be used to identify you individually. Construction Partner collects personally identifiable information from website visitors only when it is voluntarily provided. Construction Partner will not otherwise collect this information from you on our website.
At those portions of our website where we provide you with the option to input personally identifiable information, we notify you of the uses we intend to make of that information in any given instance. When Construction Partner receives personally identifiable information, we may use it for reasonable business purposes, just as non-Internet businesses do. For example, we may use this information to contact you, via email or regular mail, to provide you with information we believe may be of interest. It might also be used for compiling data and analysis to understand and serve our customers' needs. Data is also compiled to evaluate the use and utility of the services we provide online. Your information may be transferred for processing and use to Construction Partner facilities in other countries and regions of the world. Personally identifiable information will not be sold, rented or exchanged outside of Construction Partner unless the user is first notified and expressly consents to such transfer.
Collective/Aggregate Data
Construction Partner may also collect information from you that is not personally identifiable. For example, we might track information about the date and time visitors access our site, the type of web browser they used, and the website from which they connected to our site. Our website collects this information by depositing certain bits of information called "cookies" in a visitor's computer. This technology does not collect an individual visitor's personally identifiable information. Rather, this information is collected in an aggregate form. The cookies can tell us how and when pages in our website were visited and by how many people. This aggregate information will enable us to improve our website to serve and inform you better. It also may allow you shortcut access to points of interest on our website when you re-enter our system. Accepting this cooking on your system has no effect on how your computer performs.
Links To Other Websites
As a resource to our visitors, Construction Partner may provide links to other websites. We try to carefully choose websites, which we believe are useful and meet our high standards for accuracy and utility of information. However, because website design and content can change so quickly, we cannot guarantee the standards of every website to which we link. Likewise, we are not responsible for the content of any non-Construction Partner site. We also cannot guarantee the privacy policies of these other sites, and we suggest you check the privacy policies of those sites directly.
Choice
If you wish to stop receiving any emails or other communications from Construction Partner which may be sent to you in the future based on your request for this information, or if you have submitted personally identifiable information through the Construction Partner website and would like to have that information deleted from our records, please notify us via the "Contact Us" form. Your wishes in these matters will be honored.
Accuracy
Construction Partner will make every effort to maintain the accuracy and confidentiality of any personal information you supply to us. If you wish to make additions or other corrections to the information that you have sent in, please transmit it to us via the "Contact Us" form. Your wishes in these matters will be honored.
Security
All information transmitted to this Construction Partner website is secure to the extent possible using existing technology. Unauthorized third parties should not be able to access it during transmission. We will store the information that you share with us securely and will take appropriate steps to protect it from unauthorized access or disclosure. While no security steps can offer 100% protection, we utilize state-of-the-art technology and systems to prevent unauthorized access to the information we hold. We will limit access to this information to those Construction Partner personnel with a need to know. We educate our staff about their duty to protect your privacy, and provide training regarding the policy described herein.
Children
Construction Partner does not intentionally collect or retain personally identifiable information about children who are younger than 18 years of age. If your child may have submitted information to us without indicating their actual age, and you would like it removed, please advise us through the "Contact Us" form. Your wishes in these matters will be honored.
Changes
Any changes to this privacy policy will be communicated promptly at this location. Please check the privacy page periodically to review any changes that may have been made.
Thank you for visiting our Construction Partner website. We value your interest and ideas. If you have any comments or concerns regarding the use of information provided to Construction Partner via an Internet site, please contact us via the "Contact Us" form.
Request Information
800–395–7474
or
CLICK HERE
Contact  | Support |  Request Information  |  Schedule a Demo  |  Site Map  |  Privacy  |  Follow us on Twitter
Copyright ©2020 Construction Partner Inc. All Rights Reserved.
All trademarks are the property of their respective owners.
